{
  "LevelId": 37,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 377,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "DARINGNESS",
      "question": "uality is reflected in a person's willingness to take bold and courageous actions,"
    },
    {
      "id": 378,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "JABBERWORK",
      "question": "playful term is sometimes used to describe excessive or nonsensical talk,"
    },
    {
      "id": 379,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "FABULATORS",
      "question": "who are known for inventing or embellishing stories"
    },
    {
      "id": 380,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "HARVESTERS",
      "question": "term is used to describe machines or individuals involved in gathering crops"
    },
    {
      "id": 381,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "HARVESTMAN",
      "question": "common name for a long-legged arachnid that is often mistaken for a spider"
    },
    {
      "id": 382,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "CELLOPHANE",
      "question": "transparent, thin, and flexible material is commonly used for packaging"
    },
    {
      "id": 383,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "AIRDROPPED",
      "question": "In humanitarian efforts or military operations, what term is used to describe the delivery"
    },
    {
      "id": 384,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "BACKSPACED",
      "question": "action involves erasing or deleting the character"
    },
    {
      "id": 385,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "AUTOSPORTS",
      "question": "term encompasses various forms of competitive motor racing,"
    },
    {
      "id": 386,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "BALDHEADED",
      "question": "you describe someone with little to no hair on their scalp,"
    },
    {
      "id": 387,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "BACTERIALS",
      "question": "microorganisms are typically unicellular and prokaryotic,"
    },
    {
      "id": 388,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "GRASSHOPPER",
      "question": "insect, known for its jumping abilities and distinctive chirping sound,"
    }
  ]
}